<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>user, Author at US Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://us.online.mills.edu/author/user/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://us.online.mills.edu/author/user/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 16:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Australia crush India, claim World Test Championship title</title>
		<link>https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/australia-crush-india-claim-world-test-championship-title/</link>
					<comments>https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/australia-crush-india-claim-world-test-championship-title/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 16:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://us.online.mills.edu/?p=24</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Boland sparked a dramatic collapse as a dominant Australia hammered India by 209 runs to win the World Test Championship final at The Oval on Sunday. India, set a record 444 to win, resumed on 164-3. But they collapsed to 234 all out, losing seven wickets for 70 runs inside 24 overs before lunch ... <a title="Australia crush India, claim World Test Championship title" class="read-more" href="https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/australia-crush-india-claim-world-test-championship-title/" aria-label="More on Australia crush India, claim World Test Championship title">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/australia-crush-india-claim-world-test-championship-title/">Australia crush India, claim World Test Championship title</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu">US Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Scott Boland sparked a dramatic collapse as a dominant Australia hammered India by 209 runs to win the World Test Championship final at The Oval on Sunday.</p>
<p>India, set a record 444 to win, resumed on 164-3.</p>
<p>But they collapsed to 234 all out, losing seven wickets for 70 runs inside 24 overs before lunch on the fifth day.</p>
<p>Boland did the initial damage with two wickets in an over, including the prize scalp of Virat Kohli, on his way to figures of 3-46 in 16 overs.</p>
<p>Off-spinner Nathan Lyon (4-41) then polished off the tail.</p>
<p>Victory meant Australia had now captured the one major men’s cricket title that had previously eluded them.</p>
<p>“That was good fun, it was nice,” Boland told Sky Sports. “It felt pretty good to get Kohli out.</p>
<p>The 34-year-old seamer has now taken 33 wickets in eight Tests at the remarkably low average of 14.57.</p>
<p>“I have been playing state cricket for Victoria for 12 years. I have done some hard work and it is nice to play international cricket and get some wickets,” said Boland.</p>
<p>This result left India, defeated by New Zealand in the inaugural 2021 WTC final in Southampton, still searching for the first piece of global silverware in a decade.</p>
<div id="1b278994-bf5c-49a5-ba4d-f9748442f78b">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>India’s target of 444 was way in excess of the highest score made by any side to win in the fourth innings in 146 years of Test history. the West Indies’ 418-7 against Australia at St John’s in 2003</p>
<p>Australia were in charge of this final from early on with both player-of-the-match Travis Head (163) and star batsman Steve Smith (121) making hundreds in a first-innings total of 469 after India captain Rohit Sharma won the toss.</p>
<p>“It was a tough one,” said India skipper Rohit Sharma at the presentation ceremony.</p>
<p>“We bowled pretty well in the first session. Then we let ourselves down a little bit with how he bowled.”</p>
<p>Rohit, who lauded Smith and Head for their centuries, added: “In the second innings, we didn’t apply ourselves with the bat.”</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="b815a19c-0029-4ca0-b745-0f3dc3606f04">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>India were also attempting to top a ground record stretching back more than a century, with the highest successful fourth-innings chase in a Test at the Oval the 263 posted by England in a one-wicket win over Australia back in 1902.</p>
<p>And yet thousands of their fans, as they had done during the first four days, still streamed into the ground hoping their side might pull off an extraordinary win, with chants of “Kohli, Kohli, Kohli” rang out round the ground as the former India captain and Ajinkya Rahane walked out to bat.</p>
<p>Kohli had added just five runs to his overnight score when, on 49, his edged drive off a wide ball from paceman Boland was brilliantly caught by Steve Smith, diving to his right at second slip.</p>
<p>Two balls later, new batsman Ravindra Jadeja fell for a duck, caught behind after nicking a superb Boland delivery that seamed away against the angle.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="338bca8d-d7c4-4577-aabc-31be55a81ad2">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>India were now 179-5 and a sensational seventh over of the day almost ended with another wicket for Boland, when a sharply rising ball took the shoulder of Bharat’s bat before looping over David Warner at first slip.</p>
<p>Rahane, who had marked his first Test in over a year by top-scoring with patient 89 in India’s first was still there but an otherwise composed 46 ended when he went for a booming drive off fast bowler Mitchell Starc only to edge straight to wicketkeeper Alex Carey.</p>
<p>India’s 212-6 was soon transformed into 213-7 when Shardul Thakur was lbw to Lyon and the end came when Mohammed Siraj was caught reverse-sweeping the spinner.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/australia-crush-india-claim-world-test-championship-title/">Australia crush India, claim World Test Championship title</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu">US Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/australia-crush-india-claim-world-test-championship-title/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>‘History hovering’ over Djokovic as Grand Slam record beckons</title>
		<link>https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/history-hovering-over-djokovic-as-grand-slam-record-beckons/</link>
					<comments>https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/history-hovering-over-djokovic-as-grand-slam-record-beckons/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 16:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://us.online.mills.edu/?p=21</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Novak Djokovic admits “history is hovering” over him as he takes on Casper Ruud in the French Open final on Sunday with a men’s record 23rd Grand Slam title tantalisingly close. The 36-year-old Serb can set numerous landmarks in what will be his seventh championship match at Roland Garros. As well as breaking the 22-Slam ... <a title="‘History hovering’ over Djokovic as Grand Slam record beckons" class="read-more" href="https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/history-hovering-over-djokovic-as-grand-slam-record-beckons/" aria-label="More on ‘History hovering’ over Djokovic as Grand Slam record beckons">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/history-hovering-over-djokovic-as-grand-slam-record-beckons/">‘History hovering’ over Djokovic as Grand Slam record beckons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu">US Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Novak Djokovic admits “history is hovering” over him as he takes on Casper Ruud in the French Open final on Sunday with a men’s record 23rd Grand Slam title tantalisingly close.</p>
<p>The 36-year-old Serb can set numerous landmarks in what will be his seventh championship match at Roland Garros.</p>
<p>As well as breaking the 22-Slam tie he shares with Rafael Nadal, he can become both the tournament’s oldest champion and the only man to win all four majors on at least three occasions.</p>
<p>In the women’s game, only Margaret Court, Steffi Graf and Serena Williams can make a similar boast.</p>
<p>“The only thing I can say is that I’m very focused. History is always something that’s hovering over me,” said Djokovic, the 2016 and 2021 winner in Paris and now the oldest finalist in 93 years.</p>
<p>Djokovic, playing his 34th Grand Slam final, can also return to the world number one ranking with victory over Ruud, replacing Carlos Alcaraz, the man he defeated in the semi-finals.</p>
<p>Victory on Sunday would place him once again halfway to an historic calendar Grand Slam, a sweep of all four majors in the same year which has only ever been achieved by two men.</p>
<p>Rod Laver accomplished it twice, the last coming in 1969.</p>
<p>Djokovic, however, refuses to contemplate such dominance, wary of how the pressure doomed his last bid to pocket all four Slams in the same year when he lost the 2021 US Open final to Daniil Medvedev.</p>
<p>“I’m not thinking about a calendar Slam. I’m thinking really just to win another Grand Slam title here on Sunday, and I’m so close. I know it. I know the feeling,” said Djokovic.</p>
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-title">
<h2>‘Talk about history’</h2>
</div>
</div>
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>“Experience is on my side, but does it win matches? I don’t think so. I have to be prepared for another long battle, and after the final, if I win, let’s talk about history.”</p>
<p>Ruud was runner-up to Rafael Nadal in the 2022 final before also losing the championship match at the US Open to Alcaraz.</p>
<p>The 24-year-old Norwegian has never defeated Djokovic in four meetings and has yet to win a set.</p>
<p>If that wasn’t intimidating enough, just the presence of Djokovic on the other side of the net presents another challenge.</p>
<div id="2054124d-d405-44a9-922a-bf7339cf58e7">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS KMFZK qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>Alcaraz admitted that the tension he felt in facing the Serb for the first time in a Grand Slam match caused the body cramps which torpedoed his hopes in the semi-final.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="97d620c8-150b-4da5-951f-cb2427ff6293">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>“Novak is a legend of our sport,” said Alcaraz. “If someone says that he goes onto the court with no nerves playing against Novak, he lies.</p>
<p>“Of course playing a semi-final of a Grand Slam, you have a lot of nerves, but even more facing Novak. That’s the truth.”</p>
<p>As Djokovic eventually cruised to victory in Friday’s semi-final, winning 10 of the last 11 games against an ailing Alcaraz, he was booed for fist-pumping as victory closed in.</p>
<p>However, he is so used to being the pantomime villain of the sport, that it’s become an inspiration.</p>
<p>“I don’t mind. It’s not the first; probably not the last. I’ll just keep winning,” he warned.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="c6b5ad87-5f80-4c11-8ba1-d88e25f82eae">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-title">
<h2>‘Novak only human’</h2>
</div>
</div>
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>Despite Ruud’s desperately poor record against Djokovic, he can point to his prowess on clay.</p>
<p>Since 2020, he has the most wins on the surface with 87, most finals with 12 and nine titles.</p>
<p>On Sunday, the world number four will attempt to make sure that all the pressure sits squarely on the shoulders of Djokovic.</p>
<p>“I think it’s just a matter of not thinking like, I ‘need’ to win this match. This is a word that I try to avoid,” he said.</p>
<p>Alexander Zverev, defeated in straight sets by Ruud in the semi-finals, believes that Djokovic might crack under the weight of expectation.</p>
<p>“If I would have to bet money, maybe I wouldn’t bet on Casper too much. Does he have chances? Yes, he does,” said Zverev after a third successive semi-final loss in Paris.</p>
<p>“But I think it couldn’t be better for Casper. Novak is one of the best players in the world, that’s for sure, but when you’re on the brink of history I think that adds a little bit of pressure.</p>
<p>“You remember the US Open final he had with Medvedev? The pressure, you know, we are all human. Novak is human.”</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/history-hovering-over-djokovic-as-grand-slam-record-beckons/">‘History hovering’ over Djokovic as Grand Slam record beckons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu">US Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/history-hovering-over-djokovic-as-grand-slam-record-beckons/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man City beat Inter to lift maiden Champions League</title>
		<link>https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/man-city-beat-inter-to-lift-maiden-champions-league/</link>
					<comments>https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/man-city-beat-inter-to-lift-maiden-champions-league/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 16:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://us.online.mills.edu/?p=18</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Manchester City ended a sensational season by beating Inter Milan 1-0 to win the UEFA Champions League for the first time and complete the treble on a Saturday evening of frayed nerves. Spanish midfielder Rodri’s 68th-minute goal settled a cagey game which a far-from-fluent City dominated without ever looking comfortable against the three-times winners from ... <a title="Man City beat Inter to lift maiden Champions League" class="read-more" href="https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/man-city-beat-inter-to-lift-maiden-champions-league/" aria-label="More on Man City beat Inter to lift maiden Champions League">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/man-city-beat-inter-to-lift-maiden-champions-league/">Man City beat Inter to lift maiden Champions League</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu">US Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Manchester City ended a sensational season by beating Inter Milan 1-0 to win the UEFA Champions League for the first time and complete the treble on a Saturday evening of frayed nerves.</p>
<p>Spanish midfielder Rodri’s 68th-minute goal settled a cagey game which a far-from-fluent City dominated without ever looking comfortable against the three-times winners from Italy at the Ataturk Stadium.</p>
<p>Inter almost levelled at the death when a point-blank header by substitute Romelu Lukaku was saved by Ederson.</p>
<p>But City, who lost in the final two years ago against Chelsea, would not be denied.</p>
<p>“Emotional. A dream come true. All these guys around here waited I don’t know how many years. They deserve, we deserve,” Rodri said.</p>
<p>In being crowned champions of Europe, they matched the treble achieved by Manchester United in 1999 of lifting the Premier League, FA Cup and Champions League crowns.</p>
<p>City manager Pep Guardiola has now won the Champions League three times and took his trophy count with City to 12.</p>
<p>It was far from a fluent City performance, however, against a tireless Inter side who looked capable of causing a shock.</p>
<p>City were stifled in the first half and their fans were reduced to near silence at times as the nerves became frayed.</p>
<p>With Kevin de Bruyne off injured, City struggled to create chances and were wobbly at the back but in the end the ever-reliable Rodri came to the rescue.</p>
<div id="4209353d-2ff6-495b-97dc-0b2d60c42269">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS KMFZK qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>For once Inter could not close down the spaces and Bernardo Silva’s cutback was swept home by the Spaniard.</p>
<p>Even then, City were forced to go to the wire at the end of long season with Lautaro Martinez hitting the bar for Inter and Lukaku denied by s superb Ederson save at the death.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="20864eba-b5e7-44ab-8655-182781863c60">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>In finally guiding Manchester City to the European crown they so cherished after a few gut-wrenching near misses since Sheikh Mansour bought the club in 2008, Guardiola became the first manager to achieve two trebles in European football, having done the Spanish equivalent with Barcelona in 2009.</p>
<p>He has won 12 trophies with City since taking charge in 2016 and with the Champions League jinx broken, any sense of inferiority City may have suffered to the established European royalty of Real Madrid, Bayern Munich and Liverpool has gone.</p>
<p>City still must defend themselves against more than 100 alleged breaches of Premier League financial regulations dating back to 2009, but that is for another day.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="c208b828-c818-435e-adbb-c96638c8750e">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>On Saturday alongside the Bosphorous, that was the last thing City’s joyous fans cared about as they celebrated the club’s first European trophy since the now defunct European Cup Winners’ Cup in 1969–70.</p>
<p>Guardiola’s side fluffed their lines in Porto two years ago when losing to Chelsea in the Champions League final &#8211; a defeat partially blamed on Guardiola’s tactics.</p>
<p>This time he and his players delivered, although it was far from straightforward against the wily Italian side.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/man-city-beat-inter-to-lift-maiden-champions-league/">Man City beat Inter to lift maiden Champions League</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://us.online.mills.edu">US Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://us.online.mills.edu/2023/06/11/man-city-beat-inter-to-lift-maiden-champions-league/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
